Guide to the Judith Hancock de Sandoval papers and photographs
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Judith Hancock de Sandoval papers and photographs
1907-1997
1984-1990
WA MSS S-3001
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
16.4
(32 boxes) + 68 broadsides
The collection consists of material created and accumulated by Judith Hancock de Sandoval in the course of her activities as a photographer, and primarily documents her project, Historic Ranches of Wyoming, from 1984 to 1990. Material includes correspondence, notes, research files, printed material, and maps as well as photographic prints, negatives, contact sheets, slides, and printer's plates for the production of Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986). Also included are posters and publicity material for United States and international photography shows as well as video recordings, including VHS and U-matic videocassettes, and other material related to the video production Ranches of Wyoming.
Sandoval, Judith Hancock de
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Box 66: Restricted fragile material. For further information consult Access Services.
Box 100 (videocassettes): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Judith Hancock de Sandoval
Judith Hancock de Sandoval is an American photographer, writer, and historian. Sandoval was born in New York City and graduated from Ohio Wesleyan University in 1958. Since 1967 she has completed surveys of historical architecture and other photography projects in the United States and Latin America.
Arrangement
Organized into two groupings: June 2002 Acquisition and June 2012 Acquisition.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of material created and accumulated by Judith Hancock de Sandoval in the course of her activities as a photographer, and primarily documents her project, Historic Ranches of Wyoming, from 1984 to 1990. Material includes correspondence, notes, research files, printed material, and maps as well as photographic prints, negatives, contact sheets, slides, and printer's plates for the production of Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986). Also included are posters and publicity material for United States and international photography shows as well as video recordings, including VHS and U-matic videocassettes, and other material related to the video production Ranches of Wyoming.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Bonanza Group on the William Robertson Coe Fund No.3, 2002, and gift of Judith Hancock de Sandoval, 2012.
Dude ranches -- Wyoming; Historic buildings -- Wyoming -- Pictorial works; Photographers -- United States; Ranch houses -- Wyoming -- Pictorial works; Ranch life -- Wyoming -- History; Ranchers -- United States; Ranches -- Wyoming -- Pictorial works; Women photographers -- United States; Wyoming -- History; Wyoming -- Maps; Wyoming -- Pictorial works; Audiovisual materials -- United States -- 20th Century; Gelatin silver prints -- United States -- 20th Century; Maps (documents) -- United States -- 20th Century; Negatives (photographic) -- United States -- 20th Century; Photographs -- United States -- 20th Century; Slides (photographs) -- United States -- 20th Century; Videocassettes -- United States -- 20th Century; Photographers -- United States -- 20th Century; Ranchers -- United States -- 20th Century; Sandoval, Judith Hancock de
- June 2002 Acquisition, 1907-1997; 16.2; (31 boxes) and 68 broadsides
  Scope and Contents
  Notes and research files, photographs, negatives, slides, videocassette tapes, posters, printers' plates, maps, printed material, and ephemera by or relating to Judith Hancock de Sandoval and her photographic project, Historic Ranches of Wyoming.
  Arrangement
  Organized into five series: Papers and Realia, Photographs, Printed Material, Publishing Material, and Audiovisual Material.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Purchased from Bonanza Group on the William Robertson Coe Fund No.3, 2002.
  - Papers and Realia, 1963-1997; Series I; 7.5; (11 boxes)
    - National Trust Historic Preservation information, undated (Box 56)
    - Information and correspondence relating to Texas, South Dakota, Nebraska, and Colorado, 1984-1985 (Box 56)
    - Survey forms and historic preservation plans, undated (Box 56)
    - Historic preservation, various projects including "Barn Again", circa 1986 (Box 56)
    - American west and south, undated (Box 56)
    - Vernacular forum, 1985 (Box 56)
    - Development of Western Ranches project correspondence, information from various western states, including correspondence with Jack Boucher (HABS) and Ford Peatross (Library of Congress), 1983-1984 (Box 56)
    - National Register of Historic Places application South Dakota Finnish Farms, 1984-1987 (Box 57)
    - Historic preservation Wyoming state constitution rural preservation National Trust information, undated (Box 57)
    - Rural educational farm in Kentucky, 1984 (Box 57)
    - Wyoming biography, undated (Box 57)
    - Historic Ranches of Wyoming, exhibition and archive, descriptive materials, undated (Box 57)
    - Wyoming promotional materials, Nebraska, etc., 1986 (Box 57)
    - Mack Junge review of Historic Ranches of Wyoming and Sandoval's rebuttal, 1987 (Box 57)
    - Sandoval lists of ranches visited and photographed 1984-1985 (Box 57)
    - Sonny Reisch list of historic sites in Sheridan County, undated (Box 57)
    - SHPO office list of sites in National Register, 1985 (Box 57)
    - Research materials for Historic Ranches of Wyoming, undated (Box 57)
    - Comments and edits for Sandoval's text for Historic Ranches of Wyoming, 1986 (Box 57)
    - Reviews for Historic Ranches of Wyoming shows and book, 1986-1992 (Box 57)
    - Sandoval, Judith Hancock. Historic Ranches of Wyoming. Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986. 2 copies. (Box 57)
    - Correspondence with Chris LeDoux, undated (Box 57)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1986-1989 (Box 58)
    - Wyoming, articles and pamphlets, undated (Box 58)
    - Farming and ranch information from county AG extension agency. Wheatland, Wyoming, 1985 June 16 (Box 58)
    - Notes, newspaper clippings, Dubois area and Lander, ranches, builders, undated (Box 58)
    - Fish and game information, undated (Box 58)
    - Newspaper clippings on Wyoming farms and ranches, WY and NY sources, 1985-1997 (Box 58)
    - UCross/Big Red, undated (Box 58)
    - Sublette county information, undated (Box 58)
    - Old Time Ranch Tours in Albany County out of Laramie, Wyoming, and to tie camps, 1963-1984 (Box 58)
    - Important documents
      - Sandoval field notes: notebooks including interviews with ranchers and others; notes comparing sites, regions and buildings, local history, lists of sites and informants, undated (Box 59)
      - Wyoming ranch National Register of Historic Places survey forms completed, 1985 (Box 59)
      - Wyoming maps and sources of maps, circa 1978-1986 (Box 60)
      - Original letters from ranches, Sandoval's notes and letters to ranches in various counties, 1984-1986 (Box 61)
      - Sandoval's field notes, 1984-1986 (Box 62)
      - Platte county information, undated (Box 62)
      - Research from the Bancroft Library, correspondence 19th and early 20th century Wyoming ranches, 1989 (Box 62)
    - Administrative records
      - Wyoming correspondence, development of ranches project (beginnings), 1984-1985 (Box 63)
      - Ranches project 1987 fundraising efforts for U.S. Wyoming archive purchase (Box 63)
      - Wyoming correspondence, original letters, 1984-1990 (Box 63)
      - University of Wyoming correspondence, circa 1984-1987 (Box 63)
      - Wyoming letters, budgets, survey forms, and other information, 1985-1990 (Box 63)
      - Wyoming financial reports, invoices, and proposals for funding, 1985-1986 (Box 63)
      - Wyoming ranches grant applications, 1985-1987 (Box 63)
      - Wyoming show funding, 1985-1991 (Box 63)
      - Nicolaysen lawsuit, 1985-1987 (Box 63)
      - Redle protest, 1987 (Box 63)
      - Mark Junge letters, undated (Box 63)
    - Wyoming ranch project fundraising efforts, 1984-1987 (Box 64)
    - Correspondence and project proposals related to Wyoming ranches project, 1986-1988 (Box 64)
    - Financial records and AMC reports, 1985-1991 (Box 64)
    - Jackson Hole Wildlife Film Festival information, 1991 (Box 65)
    - Promotion and fundraising for ranches tour in Europe, 1984-1992 (Box 65)
    - Wyoming ranches European tour materials, 1989-1993 (Box 65)
    - Wyoming exhibition materials, 1987-1991 (Box 65)
    - Introduction and maps for Wyoming exhibition, undated
    - TV and film correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 65)
    - Material relating to Wyoming videos, 1986-1990 (Box 65)
    - Video script and list of slides given to K2TV for Ranches of Wyoming video, 1986 (Box 65)
    - Video correspondence and contracts, 1986 (Box 65)
    - TV film prospectus, 1986 (Box 65)
    - Funding for film, 1985-1986 (Box 65)
    - Wyoming State Historical Society, Historical Award for Historic Ranches of Wyoming, 1987 (Box 65)
    - Dude ranch info, sample set, undated (Box 65)
    - Field notes and photograph lists, undated (Box 65)
    - Printing notes for black and white photographs for exhibition, 1984 (Box 65)
    - Beer bottle dug up by an old rancher at Fort Laramie, Wyoming, undated (Box 66)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted fragile material. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Photographs, 1974-1990; Series II; 5.1; (13 boxes)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheets of ranches in South Dakota and Montana, 1974 (Box 67)
    - Color prints, slides, and negatives for portraits of Sandoval and Lynch on a truck, 1990 (Box 67)
    - 8 x 10 inch black and white gelatin silver prints of Wyoming ranches in show 1-15, not in show number 16-20, 1984-1986 (Box 67)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheets, 35 mm and 120 mm, 1984-1985 (Box 68)
    - 8 x 10 inch black and white gelatin silver prints of Wyoming ranches in show catalog number 16-96, 1984-1985 (Box 69)
    - 8 x 10 inch black and white gelatin silver prints of Wyoming ranches in show catalog number 16-96, 1984-1985 (Box 70)
    - 5 sets of black and white negatives and contact sheets, 1987 (Box 70)
    - Color slides 1984-1987, also best photos for lectures in Europe 1991 (Box 70)
    - Color slides 1984-1987 (Box 71)
    - 8 x 10 inch black and white silver gelatin prints of Wyoming ranches not in show catalog number 21-138, circa 1984 (Box 72)
    - 8 x 10 inch black and white silver gelatin prints of Wyoming ranches not in show catalog number 21-138, circa 1984 (Box 73)
    - 8 x 10 inch black and white silver gelatin prints of Wyoming ranches not in show catalog number 21-138, circa 1984 (Box 74)
    - Color slides, 1985 (Box 74)
    - Color slides, 1985 (Box 75)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheets, 1984-1986 (Box 76)
    - Publicity photographs Historic Ranches of Wyoming exhibition, 15 4 x 5 inch negatives and 14 gelatin silver proof prints, undated (Box 76)
    - 1985 show photographs, black and white negatives and contact sheets (Box 76)
    - Photograph identification notes for color and black and white photographs, undated (Box 76)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheets, 1985 (Box 77)
    - 1986 color photograph lists, Headlee information, and information on Albany County ranches (Box 78)
    - Color slides 1985 and 1986 a few taken in 1989 and 1990, dude ranches in detail, 1985-1990 (Box 78)
    - Color slides 1985 and 1986 a few taken in 1989 and 1990, dude ranches in detail, 1985-1990 (Box 79)
    - 11 x 14 inch black and white gelatin silver Wyoming show prints numbers 1-39, 1986
    - 8 x 14 inch black and white gelatin silver Wyoming show prints numbers 40-68, 1986
    - 11 x 14 inch black and white gelatin silver Wyoming show prints numbers 69-96, 1986
    - 11 x 14 inch black and white gelatin silver prints, not in show, 1986
    - Color prints and 1 transparency of Wyoming ranches, undated
  - Printed Material, 1907-1995; Series III; 2; (2 boxes) and 13 broadsides
    - Pamphlets, 1978-1995 (Box 80)
    - Soft cover slim books, 1978-1995 (Box 80)
    - Wyoming magazines, 1978-1995 (Box 80)
    - Texas Heritage magazine, Spring 1984 issue
    - Wyoming publications, 1983-1990 (Box 81)
    - 1907 publication from Douglas, Wyoming
    - Tourist information, guides, undated (Box 81)
    - Wyoming maps, undated (Box 81)
    - Wyoming county maps, 1969-1980 (Box 82 (Broadside))
      Printed maps of Wyoming counties, annotated by Judith Hancock de Sandoval to identify some ranch locations.
    - Wyoming county maps, 1969-1980 (Box 83 (Broadside))
    - Wyoming county maps, 1969-1980 (Box 84 (Broadside))
    - Wyoming county maps, 1969-1980 (Box 85 (Broadside))
    - Wyoming county maps, 1969-1980 (Box 86 (Broadside))
    - Wyoming county maps, 1969-1980 (Box 87 (Broadside))
    - Wyoming county maps, 1969-1980 (Box 88 (Broadside))
    - Wyoming county maps, 1969-1980 (Box 89 (Broadside))
    - Wyoming county maps, 1969-1980 (Box 90 (Broadside))
    - Wyoming county maps, 1969-1980 (Box 91 (Broadside))
    - Historic Ranches of Wyoming show posters, U.S. and Europe, 1991-1992 (Box 92 (Broadside))
    - Historic Ranches of Wyoming show posters, U.S. and Europe, 1991-1992 (Box 93 (Broadside))
    - Posters for Nicolaysen Art Museum exhibit Historic Ranches of Wyoming, 1986 (Box 94 (Broadside))
    - Disney's Buffalo Bill posters, undated
  - Publishing Material, circa 1986; Series IV; 55 broadsides
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 1 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 2 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 3 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 4 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 5 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 6 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 7 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 8 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 9 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 10 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 11 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 12 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 13 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 14 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 15 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 16 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 17 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 18 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 19 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 20 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 21 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 22 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 23 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 24 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 25 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 26 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 27 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 28 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 29 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 30 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 31 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 32 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 33 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 34 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 35 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 36 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 37 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 38 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 39 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 40 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 41 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 42 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 43 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 44 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 45 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 46 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 47 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 48 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 49 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 50 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 51 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 52 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 53 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 54 (Broadside))
    - Printer's plates for Historic Ranches of Wyoming (Casper, Wyo.: Nicolaysen Art Museum, 1986), circa 1986 (Box 55 (Broadside))
  - Audiovisual Material, 1985-1990; Series V; 1; (1 box)
    Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Unlabeled VHS videocassette related to Wyoming, SKC T-120, undated; WAMSSS3001_0001; 1; 00:33:12 (Box 100, Item barcode 39002093673292)
    - "Ranches of Wyoming. C. Bonanza Productions (J. Sandoval). Narrator: Bob Price, K2TV Casper, Wyoming", undated; WAMSSS3001_0002; 1; 00:32:13; PAL (Box 100, Item barcode 39002093673300)
    - "Wyoming Magic. Narrated by Richard Farnsworth. Length: 29:53 Mins. Horizon Pictures.", 1990 April 9; WAMSSS3001_0003; 1; 00:30:27 (Box 100, Item barcode 39002093673318)
      A note on the tape reads: Accompanied "Historic Ranches of Wyoming" Exhibition in [?] 1991-1992
    - "Chris LeDoux 'Riding for a fall.' Time: 3:30", undated; WAMSSS3001_0004; 1; 00:05:26 (Box 100, Item barcode 39002093673326)
      Information accompanies this tape and reads: accompanied "Historic Ranches of Wyoming" exhibition in [?] 1991-1992. It also reads: famous Wyoming cowboy singer Chris LeDoux.
    - "Historic Ranches of Wyoming 35:00", undated; WAMSSS3001_0005; 1; 00:32:33; This is a Master 3/4" for "Historic Ranches of Wyoming" from K2TV, Casper, WY (Box 100, Item barcode 39002102316669)
      Bob Price is listed as the narrator.
    - "Report to Wyoming interview Judith Sandoval K2TV; Bob Price, Casper, Wyoming", 1985 May 16; WAMSSS3001_0006; 1; 00:30:21 (Box 100, Item barcode 39002102316677)
      The tape is labeled 1986-12-06 RTW; Carl Bagge coal
    - Unlabeled VHS videocassette related to Wyoming, JVC 120, undated; WAMSSS3001_0007; 1; 00:03:18; There is no sound on this tape. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002102316685)
    - "Interview Judith Sandoval 'Report to Wyoming' K2TV Bob Price, Casper, Wyoming", 1985 May 16; WAMSSS3001_0008; 1; 00:29:51 (Box 100, Item barcode 39002102316693)
    - "Sandoval", undated; WAMSSS3001_0009; 1; 00:40:20 (Box 100, Item barcode 39002102316701)
    - "Ranches of Wyoming C. Bonanza Productions. Narrator Bob Price K2TV, Casper, Wyoming. Won State Prize", undated; WAMSSS3001_0010; 1; This tape has not been digitized. It is a copy of WAMSSS30001_0002. (Box 100, Item barcode 39002102316719)
  - Oversize, 0.66; (4 boxes)
    - 11 x 14 inch black and white gelatin silver Wyoming show prints numbers 1-39, 1986 (Box 95 (Oversize))
    - 8 x 14 inch black and white gelatin silver Wyoming show prints numbers 40-68, 1986 (Box 95 (Oversize))
    - 11 x 14 inch black and white gelatin silver Wyoming show prints numbers 69-96, 1986 (Box 96 (Oversize))
    - 11 x 14 inch black and white gelatin silver prints, not in show, 1986 (Box 96 (Oversize))
    - Color prints and 1 transparency of Wyoming ranches, undated (Box 97 (Oversize))
    - 1907 publication from Douglas, Wyoming (Box 97 (Oversize))
    - Introduction and maps for Wyoming exhibition, undated (Box 98 (Oversize))
    - Texas Heritage magazine, Spring 1984 issue (Box 98 (Oversize))